There are several flavors of trading strategies.
交易策略有多种类型
The most basic type is based on buying and selling a single asset.
最基本的类型是买卖单个资产
An example of this type of strategy might be just trading the S&amp;P 500.
例如 只交易标普 500 指数
You could track the performance of the S&amp;P over
你可以跟踪标普 500 在一段时间内的业绩
time and enter positions based on past performance.
并根据历史业绩建仓
For example, if the S&amp;P has been doing well for a while,
例如 如果标普 500 一段时间以来一直表现不错
you might enter a long position under the assumption that it has momentum.
如果你认为它有动量效应(继续上涨) 那你就应该做多这个资产
Another common strategy is to find pairs of assets that seemed to be
另一个常见策略是寻找相关性强的资产
related and trade based on their relative movements.
并根据资产价格相对变动进行交易
These are called pairwise strategies.
称之为配对策略
For example, say there are two big companies in the beverage industry,
例如 假设在饮料行业有两家大公司
these companies are probably subject to many in the same market affects,
这两家公司很可能受到很多相同市场因素的影响
the price of ingredients,
例如配料价格
the cost of shipping et cetera.
运输成本 等等
If one stock starts to appreciate more than the other,
如果一支股票比另一支涨的更快
you might think that the laggard will eventually catch up.
涨的慢的股票或许之后也会赶上
A pairwise strategy would make trades to try to capture this differential.
配对策略就会做出交易 来从这种差异中获利
Another class of trading strategy extends this idea to groups of stocks,
另一种交易策略将这种理论延伸到了一组股票
these are called cross-sectional strategies also known as
称之为横截面策略
equity statistical arbitrage or equity market neutral investing.
亦称为股权统计套利或股权市场中性投资
This is a popular type of strategy and involves comparing
这是一种很流行的策略类型
hundreds to thousands of stocks to determine which to hold
需要比较成百上千支股票并决定做多和做空哪些股票
in long and short portfolios with the goal of benefiting from
通过发现瞬时的市场现象获利
transient market phenomena without being subject to overall market movements.
而免受市场整体变动的影响
The comparison is often based on price and or volume or fundamental information.
通常基于价格 成交量或基本面信息进行比较
A momentum signal where you rank stocks based on the strength of
根据在给定时间的历史收益率
prior returns over a given period is an example of a cross-sectional strategy.
对股票进行排序这种动量信号就属于横截面策略
Finally, there's a class of strategies based primarily on new types of data,
最后 还有一种基于新的数据类型的交易策略
such as satellite imagery, social media,
例如卫星图像 社交媒体
geolocation or consumer transaction data.
地理定位或消费者交易数据
Large hedge funds and asset managers are most interested in strategies three and four.
大型对冲基金和资产经理对第三种及第四种策略最感兴趣
These are the two we spend most of the time on in this nano-degree.
在这门纳米学位课程中 我们将花大部分时间介绍这两种策略
Why is this? Two reasons: first,
为何呢？原因有两个
large professional market participants by
根据定义 大型专业市场参与者
definition have large amounts of capital to put to work.
拥有大量资金
As such, they desire strategies with high capacity,
所以 他们希望采用高投资能力的策略
this means the strategy can be put to work at a meaningful asset level and
也就是说这个策略能用在大规模的资金上
this is most often achieved by trading very many stocks.
通常这种策略都会采用交易很多股票来实现
Cross-sectional strategies all other things being equal,
其他情况不变 横截面交易
have the highest capacity.
的投资能力最高
Second, professional market participants are looking for differentiated ideas.
其次 专业市场参与者希望寻找差异性的想法
Given the proliferation of alternative data,
随着另类数据的不断涌现
many funds hope to uncover signals in hard-to-find,
很多基金希望从难以寻找 成本高昂
expensive and difficult to work with data.
并且难处理的数据中发现交易信号
We will talk about that later in this nano degree.
我们将在这门课程中的后续阶段讨论这一点